tennisnow.com 2013-10-14

# Links Directory

Privacy Policy

 **TennisNow.com**  has created a privacy policy to show our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our practices on information gathering and sharing.

**Personal Information:  **  
We regard all personal information collected from visitors and members as confidential. This includes personal data provided during subscription registration and the answering of any polls/surveys. TennisNow.com may use the information for internal purposes but will not sell, loan or share your   information with any outside party. If you choose to give us your personal information, we will keep that information private unless expressly stated.

**Forums:**  
We make forums available to members. Please remember that any information disclosed in these or any other public areas becomes public information and you should use caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Advertisements:**  
The ads on our website usually contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our site, cookies from ads are collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to that information.

**External Links:**  
This site contains links to other sites and therein Tennis Now is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.

**Unsubscribe:**  

If you do not want to receive e-mails from us, you may elect to opt-out of receiving them at any time after registering by e-mailing us at [media@tennisnow.com](http://media@tennisnow.com/), by writing to us at the address contained herein, or by hitting the ["unsubscribe"](http://www.tennisnow.com/Newsletter-Signup.aspx/?firstname=%5bEMV) button at the bottom of any of our e-mails. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what e-mails you do not want to receive.

**Contacting Tennis Now:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of our site, or if you have any other questions, please contact us:

**Tennis Now**  
200 West 39th Street, Suite #11   
New York, NY 10018   
**(914) 595-4211**
